bescom.co.in 2019-12-24

# PrivacyInfo

|     | 

|  | 

|  BESCOM respects and protects the privacy of the individuals/Consumers who use Website/online services. Individually identifiable information about you is not willfully disclosed to any third party without first receiving your permission, as explained in this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy").  
---  
Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. Be aware, however, that some parts of our services may not function properly if you refuse cookies.  
Except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information, we do not collect any unique information about you (such as your name, email address, Mobile No etc.). BESCOM notes and saves information such as time of day, IP address etc with each query. This information is used to verify our records and to provide more relevant services to users. By agreeing to the Terms & Conditions of this website, you also agree to receive Email/SMS communication from BESCOM in connection with the Account ID or other general consumer information/announcements from BESCOM.  
BESCOM will not share your personal data with advertisers, sponsors, and other third parties without your express consent. Please be aware, however, that we will release specific personal information about you if required to do so in order to comply with any valid legal process such as a search warrant, court order etc.  
Your consent and changes to the Privacy Policy By using the [www.bescom.co.in](http://www.bescom.co.in/), you consent to the collection and use of your information as we have outlined in this policy and to our Terms & Conditions. BESCOM may decide to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
